watchindia.tv 2008-06-26

# WatchIndia live

|  |  |   
---|---  
|   
---  
Privacy Policy   
  
KUMARINA INVESTMENT LTD. - PRIVACY POLICY, APRIL 2007 

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

  1. Kumarina respects our subscribers' rights to privacy online and will not share, sell or otherwise distribute your information to any third party without your prior consent. In order to process client requests with minimum delay, Kumarina may request information about you. Any information you provide to Kumarina, including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will only be used internally by Kumarina to process your membership, support requests and provide you with the best customer support 

  2. We do not sell, trade, or rent your information, both personally identifiable and aggregate data, to any parties outside of Kumarina. Your name and other personal information are only used to correspond with you. 

  3. Kumarina collects user's email addresses and reserves the right to send commercial email to all registered users. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by adjusting his/her profile settings on the Site. ****

  4. Financial information that is collected is used only to check the users' qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services. ****

  5. We use the IP address of Consumers to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Site. We use the IP address of Consumers to help identify their shopping cart. ****

  6. We use cookies to keep track of shopping cart contents and/or referral information. " **Cookies** " are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to let you use our site easily and to let us keep track of certain statistical information that helps us improve the services available. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site. 

  7. You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to Kumarina. The notice we intend to provide on the Site where Kumarina collects personal information should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, you can still visit some of Kumarina's Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services that involve our interaction with you. 

|  | Terms & Conditions |  | Privacy Policy |  | Join |  | Contact |  | Support |  | Partners |  | Advertise with us |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---
